[suspenseful music]
[footsteps]
[wind blowing]
[relaxing music]
[door slamming]
You're Hunter.
I'm Elle.
[Hunter] I know.
I love you...in everything.
You don't have to
sell yourself to me.
[sigh]
I gave away my room.
That's unfortunate.
The airline lost my luggage
because of the mist.
It's been a disaster.
Aren't you the poor
little match girl.
Hans Christian Andersen.
I don't really
listen to European music.
Come on.
I'm just so excited
to be in the movie with you.
[soft romantic orchestral music]
[music continues]
Fuck me.
My room is this way.
Hey.
You know, I can stay on
the couch. It looks super comfy.
You can stay with me.
I'm just taking my face off.
Ok. Cool.
[music ends]
I don't know if
I can post these.
People will say I've
become...unrelatable.
[romantic string orchestra]
[music fades]
[bangle rattling]
Can you help me with this?
[exhaling]
You've got expensive taste.
Play date?
[Dominique] That bangle
hasn't been cool in ages.
It's for the masses.
For the masses? Oh,
you're so unrelatable.
[Dominique] Ew.
Who would want to be relatable?
Hunter wants to be relatable.
It's...
a metrics thing.
Oh...no, no, no.
You can let
the numbers measure you,
but you can't measure yourself
by the numbers.
That's wise. Did you pick
that up at a sound bath?
There's not a single person...
on this planet...
that is like you.
You're a very specific...
spec of stardust.
Stop!
No. You stop!
This means something.
[Dominique] Say it with me.
I am a wholly
unique consciousness.
I am a wholly...
And I am made...
of stardust.
I am made of stardust.
The moment you forget that
is the moment you disappear.
I'm sorry, but...who are you?
I'd like you to meet Dominique.
My step mom.
[romantic string orchestra]
But you are so young.
And you know nothing
about Johnny Thunders.
That father of mine.
[romantic music continues]
[Elle] He likes beautiful things
and beautiful people.
He's a powerful man.
[Johnny exhales]
If you think he's playing games
with you...
[chuckles]
...he is.
If you think he's being sincere
with you...
...he is.
Sometimes
he wants to impress you.
Other times he wants
to be impressed by you.
Usually the latter.
In his mind,
you either have it or you don't.
It must be genetic
because I'm the same way.
[romantic music continues]
[music fades]
Ow!
You pricked me.
Oh, dear.
I'm so sorry.
Isn't it...
a sign of good luck?
[suspenseful music]
As a matter of fact, it is.
A prick of the needle is a sign
of... success.
Fucking prick me, bitch.
Preferably...
in the eye.
Have you
experienced...misfortune?
I am a victim of the mist.
It is not the mist
you need to worry about,
it is what the mist brings.
[orchestral music continues]
It's a tragedy if you ask me.
Something no father
should have to endure.
[tense, suspenseful music]
I remember...
the day that you were born.
The day I saw the universe.
My dear, Elle...
I will always carry you.
Always.
I couldn't imagine losing you.
But if I did, I'd search
the earth until my legs stopped
working.
And if I had to
kill to find you,
I'd do it.
And I'd keep on doing it.
I would turn the oceans red
before I gave up on you.
And that...my dear girls...
...is the tragedy of The
Leatherman.
Who?
[sniffing]
[exhaling heavily]
The Leatherman is a father
searching for his daughter
lost in the underworld.
[ominous music]
A father cursed to
search for lifetimes.
Who eventually forgets
who he's looking for.
[tense drone]
But when the mist
returns, he remembers.
He remembers her.
He comes with the mist.
Searching.
His face...
an infinite abyss.
His strength insurmountable.
He wears leather gloves
covered in razor sharp diamonds,
searching for her
and any girl who sees him.
For when you see him, he sees
his daughter and he will try and
destroy you and anyone
around you to get to her.
And the only way to kill him...
...is to cut off his hands.
[tense orchestral music]
That's why they say...
take care of
your daughters. Or he will.
[music fades]
Daddy...is fascinating.
[Elle] He's just a money guy.
And you can call him Johnny.
Okay.
I wasn't expecting Johnny
to be like that one bit.
[Hunter] He is so
curious and nurturing.
He has this backwards logic
where he thinks that fucking
girls my age will somehow bring
him closer to me.
But didn't he,
like, marry Dominique?
[soft romantic orchestral music]
Why are you leaving me, Daddy?
[music fades]
[Johnny] I want you and
Dominique to be friends again.
That's a sweet fantasy.
Elle, making
a movie is like going to war.
It'll bring you girls closer.
I'm here because I wanted
to go to war with you.
I would have never have agreed
to this if I knew you were
going to go.
I'll only get in the way
of you two making up if I stay.
You girls coming together
is how we become a family again.
Dominique's one of us.
She's like us,
but she's not one of us.
There's a difference.
She loves you something fierce.
Maybe more
than she loves me.
This movie's gonna be hell.
[sighs]
[Elle exhaling]
[Elle sniffling]
Promise me you'll be a good
girl and play nice while I'm
gone. Hmm?
Hmm.
[soft orchestral music]
[music fades]
[tense drone]
[soft orchestral music]
[Hunter laughs]
[Hunter] What is she doing?
[ominous drum]
[screaming] Help me!
Help me!
Help me! Help--
[woman's head
crashing into the window]
[yelling] Daddy!
[bones breaking]
[tense orchestral music]
[pulsating sound]
[electronic button beep]
[sweeping sound]
[thrumming propulsion]
[spaceship rattling heavily]
[rattling fades]
[ominous drone]
[suspenseful music]
[dramatic
orchestral music and laser fire]
orchestral music fades]
[thud]
[calm orchestral music begins]
[Elle groaning]
[Elle breathing heavily]
[Elle winces in pain]
[dramatic
crescendo, then fading]
Just kill me.
I can't.
I'm sorry, but...
...do you guys
want to hear something scary?
[tense high strings]
[Hunter breathing heavily]
[panting]
I fell down the Leatherman
rabbit hole last night.
And everything
Johnny said is true.
And...
there are these beings...
called the kingmakers.
This pair of women,
they always come in two.
And they can be old or young.
Hideous or beautiful.
And sometimes...
they can even
become shape shifting foxes.
With multiple tails.
Magic foxes?
[Hunter] Yes.
And they are the guides
for the Leatherman.
And they are
neither good nor evil.
Neutral.
Morally ambiguous.
[Hunter] This is legit.
This leather guy
has been around for like, ever.
Some cultures
call him the leather King,
but most people...
...call him...
...the devil.
Oh...no, not the devil.
And it's these
magical lady foxes
who help him find his destroyer.
They are the ones who make him.
And they are the ones...
[high-pitched
voice] who end him!
I just want you to understand
that what we saw
was not a normal murder.
[music fades]
What the fuck
is a normal murder?
I feel like you two should be
a bit more traumatized by this.
Trauma comes in all forms.
I mean, I couldn't even pretend
to kill Elle today.
I really think
we saw the Leatherman.
[suspenseful orchestral music]
[music fades]
[Johnny] Elle.
[Johnny]  Sad to miss
your big day tomorrow,
but happy that we can bury
the hatchet.
Use it with love. Daddy.
[shower running]
[orchestral music]
[sigh]
[music fades]
[ominous, wind-like ambience]
[lighter clicks shut]
[exhales]
[suspenseful orchestral music]
[Private K] I
saw the Leatherman.
I saw him take my daughter.
Is he a ghost?
A monster? A God?
I don't know.
[music fades]
But what I do know is
the mist has returned.
Girls are dying.
I'll never stop
searchin for her.
Compliments of Uncle Sam.
[orchestral music]
[music fades]
[engine roars]
[soft piano]
[suspenseful orchestral music]
[woman screams]
[orchestral music intensifies]
[woman screaming]
[music softens
to a few instruments]
[music fades]
[cicadas chirping]
[chains rattling]
[flash, heavy thud]
[camera shutter clicks]
[Private K in English]  People
tell me I have a death wish.
[orchestral music]
[camera shutter clicks]
I've thought about it.
Figured if I died...
And go to hell.
If I went to hell...
I could find the Leatherman.
If I found him...
I could kill him.
Kill him and bring her back.
I can't tell you.
Not now.
Hell...
can wait.
[men groaning]
[Private K yells]
[music shifts to
suspenseful orchestral]
[chains rattling]
[man groaning]
[buttons clicking]
[jukebox starts,
instrumental pop music]
[Private K yells]
[Taoka laughing]
[groaning]
[music continues]
[Taoka yells]
[Taoka screams]
[man with sword screaming]
[fighting sounds continue]
[groaning]
[music swells]
[Taoka straining]
[music ends]
[footsteps]
[man straining and groaning]
[man on floor groaning]
[subtle orchestral strings]
[man] You really
fucked up this time.
I'm sympathetic
to your situation.
Losing a child the way you did.
Well, the Yakuza is one thing...
but our friends at the police
department...
...they can't have the men
mistake mercy for weakness.
[lighter flicks]
Compliments of Uncle Sam.
[music fades]
Hm-mh.
[belt strikes his back]
Daddy. Daddy.
Daddy.
[belt strikes his back]
[dreamy orchestral music]
[Ms. T] It is not the mist
you need to worry about.
It is what the mist brings.
[Johnny] When the mist returns,
he remembers.
[Elle] Daddy! Daddy!
[Dominique] And he will destroy
everything and everyone in
his path to get to her.
[Johnny] Take care
of your daughters...
or he will.
[music fades]
[Elle laughs]
It's a bit performative...
but it's tradition.
[growling and barking]
[Dominique barking]
[barking]
[barking continues]
[Dominique and Elle howling]
[Dominique and Elle panting]
[laughing]
[soft romantic music]
That's so cool.
You guys speak Wolf.
We used to
speak it all the time.
[Dominique] It's
our secret language.
You know...
when I first met Elle,
she told me she was an orphan.
So I bought
her drinks all night.
My little match girl.
She got so drunk,
I had to bring her home.
And she threw up
all over me and my bed.
And we've loved
each other ever since.
[music fades]
I want to be an orphan, too.
Should we play orphans tonight?
Niko's in town.
[Dominique] He'd
probably adopt all of us.
The...Nico?
Put your tongue
back in your mouth.
[Dominique] Oh! Come on.
I adore Niko, and he's
always wanted to meet you.
Of course he wants to meet me.
He famously hates my father.
I read that.
[Dominique]
I gave our driver the night off.
No need having one of my
husband's snitches keeping
tabs on us.
I'm going home.
You really want
the night to end?
[whimpering]
[barking softly]
[wordless female
choir over a beat]
Your fucking dad,
Johnny Thunders,
is a sick motherfucker.
Hi.
I like freaky shit. Okay?
Like the real freak shit.
But Johnny, he's next level.
We were in this...
lesbian they/them performance.
Actually, it was pretty
interesting.
Fucking grungy crowd.
And in the corner of the whole
thing, there was Johnny.
And Johnny was pointing
right at me. Like, right at me.
You want to see something scary?
Next thing I know, I'm in this
art studio behind a dumpling
store in Chinatown,
watching a super art
installation about one of
the greatest living artists
tattooing a skull
on a fucking fetus.
Ew! Like a baby?
Like a dead baby, yeah.
-[Dominique] And Johnny
saw this? -[Nico] Oh, yes.
He bought it right there.
Paid like 10 grand for it. Cash.
Do you know about this?
Have you seen the fetus?
My father protects me.
Well...
aren't you Daddy's little baby.
[Dominique chuckles]
I might even tell him about how
you can't keep your hands off
my stepmom.
[Nico] Hunter. What's this scary
thing you want to tell me about?
[Hunter] Oh,
my gosh, it was so scary.
Have you heard
about the Leatherman?
[music fades]
[Nico] What?
[Hunter] The Leatherman.
[ominous, wind-like ambience]
[footsteps approaching]
[suspenseful tremolo strings]
[Private K] Death has its time.
My daughter didn't get
a second more than what was due.
[strings fade,
leaving wind-like ambience]
If I could sweep
the pain off her feet, I would.
Body's fault the time.
Memories fault the time.
But I know
that time bows to love.
And love only.
[low, ominous piano notes]
[suspenseful orchestral music]
[music fades]
Yoko isn't here tonight.
It's been a difficult time for
you...
Private K.
I know your heart
has been blackened by grief.
Most people...
choose to live in a
comfortable amount of pain.
But you...
Private K, you have
chosen to live in agony.
You're just
a memory you won't let go of.
That won't work on us.
We know your girl
is a strong child,
a resilient one.
[low, ominous piano]
Her will alone has
kept her blood warm.
All these years.
We know that she is
not far from you.
[ominous piano
builds into orchestral music]
She is in his kingdom.
His kingdom in the mist. And the
mist...
is right in front of you.
The Leatherman must die.
And then, and only then
will you see your daughter.
[music fades]
[dramatic orchestral music]
[groaning]
[panting]
[music intensifies]
[yelling]
[music ends]
[Ms. T] But remember Private
K...
to catch a ghost...
you must become a ghost.
[orchestral music]
A gift for my pup.
You know this
isn't going to work.
What isn't going to work?
This movie
isn't going to fix us.
[music fades out]
I have no
misconceptions about fixing us.
I don't love
you for you to love me back.
I just do.
[Elle] Christ.
That girl is fucking unbearable.
[Dominique sighs]
She's really
begging to be touched.
Imagine being that attractive,
yet that unfuckable.
[Dominique]
Ouch! Well, aren't you evil?
I slept with
Nico the other night.
That is vile.
Opposite. He tasted like soap.
That's even worse somehow.
I kind of like
the way he tastes.
Does Johnny know?
Your father and
I enjoy our secrets.
It's a part of our contract.
But we don't lie.
Not to each other and
not to anyone else.
Except for that one time.
[romantic orchestral music]
Do you feel like I replaced you?
No one could replace you, Elle.
Not to him and not to me.
Did you think that marrying my
father would bring me
closer to you?
That's one way to look at it.
Maybe that was
a part of the appeal.
You could have just
copied my shoes, or my hair.
I did. So did you.
Honestly, Elle, I've been
mothering you since
the day we met.
How is this any different?
[sighs] I can't believe
you actually admitted that.
I know being best friends again
might be a bit out of reach.
But...
I will always...
...be your evil stepmother.
[kiss]
[Elle sighs]
This family is rotten.
[Dominique laughs]
[Dominique]  I should
probably save her from him.
[Elle] Or him from her.
You're free to go.
I can distract Nico.
[Hunter exhales]
Nico says nothing spontaneous
happens at these private
parties.
And we should go
to the uniform night.
What happens at uniform night?
Nico?
[industrial elevator rumbling]
[ominous synth tones]
[techno music]
[techno music becomes muffled]
[techno music
fades into ominous music]
[Dominique] Missed you.
I'm not in the mood.
[instrumental pop music]
[pop music fades
into ominous music]
[music ends]
[ominous ambience]
[moaning]
[Elle moaning]
[Elle breathing heavily]
[music becomes happy orchestral]
[cheerful music
fades to ominous]
[ominous music
fades back to cheerful]
[ominous music]
[both breathing heavily]
[heavy breathing]
[ominous music intensifies]
[thud]
[Elle moaning]
Daddy.
[ripping sound]
[optimistic orchestral music]
[music fades]
[orchestral music]
[sigh]
[breathing heavily]
[muffled scream]
Can you taste him?
Can you taste the soap?
Your father's gonna love this.
Oh, yeah? Yeah,
you're gonna tell on me?
You're gonna be
a little tattletale!
Elle. I don't want you.
There's nothing you want or have
that doesn't belong to me.
You will never be one of us!
You're just a possession.
All worn out. Dried up.
You're something that my father
will fucking throw away.
Toxic fucking waste!
You think you're so special.
Somehow everyone else
seems to think so too.
But I see you.
I used to think
we were the same.
But I don't bask in self-doubt
and pity. I don't wallow about
my own father.
I write my own fucking story.
I've recreated myself.
I used to wonder
how it was possible for someone
who had it all
to be so cruel and insecure.
And then I met you.
And I have never met someone
so empty and disappointing.
You won't feel fucking whole
until you wear my fucking skin!
Money won't fucking fix it!
Enlightenment won't fix it!
My daddy won't fucking fix it!
Your daddy?
You know, the other day,
after your daddy fucked me,
he confessed something.
He told me how painful,
how sickening it is
to come face to face with all
the things he hates the most
about himself in you.
He looks at you, and all he sees
is this gaping maw of misery
and need.
No wonder he's always leaving.
He cannot stand the fucking
sight of you.
Fuck!
Fucking psycho.
[Elle yells]
Back the fuck off, bitch!
[laughing]
[breathes out heavily]
[huffs]
Don't bring a knife
to a fucking axe fight, you
fucking...
bitch!
[laughing hysterically]
[laughing continues]
[yells]
I could kill her!
[dramatic orchestral music]
[crying hysterically]
[hysterical crying continues]
[ominous music]
[Dominique screaming]
[Dominique] Elle!
[pounding]
[Dominique screaming]
[Dominique
screaming] Open the door!
[Dominique screaming]
No, Daddy!
[pounding on door]
[Dominique pounding on door
and screaming]
[pounding and noises stop]
[loud crack]
[intense orchestral choir music]
[music fades]
[ominous music]
[Elle breathes nervously]
[nervous breathing]
[dramatic orchestral music]
[music intensifies]
[music fades]
[axe clatters to the floor]
[hymn-like
orchestral music builds]
[music fades]
We don't often...
get to choose our fate.
But you have
always been special, Elle.
After all,
you were pricked by
the needle of success.
If you were to put these gloves
on...
you will find
what you have lost.
[orchestral music]
[instrumental pop music]